<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-11-05T00:19:35+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Defining the future: The talks of TED Salon: Dell Technologies</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/29/post6.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Defining the future: The talks of TED Salon: Dell Technologies" /><published>2020-10-29T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-29T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/29/post6</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/29/post6.html">&lt;p&gt;In a time that feels unsettled and uncertain, technology and those who create it will play a crucial role in what’s coming next. How do we define that future, as opposed to letting it define us? At a special TED Salon held as part of the Dell Technologies World conference and hosted by TED’s Simone Ross, four speakers shared ideas for building a future where tech and humanity are combined in a more active, deliberate and thoughtful way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The talks in brief:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Genevieve Bell, ethical AI expert&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big idea: To create a sustainable, efficient and safe future for artificial intelligence systems, we need to ask questions that contextualize the history of technology and create possibilities for the next generation of critical thinkers to build upon it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How? Making a connection between AI and the built world is a hard story to tell, but that’s exactly what Genevieve Bell and her team at 3A Institute are doing: adding to the rich legacy of AI systems, while establishing a new branch of engineering that can sustainably bring cyber-physical systems and AI to scale going forward. “To build on that legacy and our sense of purpose, I think we need a clear framework for asking questions about the future, questions for which there aren’t ready or easy answers,” Bell says. She shares six nuanced questions that frame her approach: Is the system autonomous? Does the system have agency? How do we think about assurance (is it safe and functioning)? How do we interface with it? What will be the indicators that show it is working well? And finally, what is its intent? With these questions, we can broaden our understanding of the systems we create and how they will function in the years to come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amanda Little, food journalist&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big idea: To build a robust, resilient and diverse food future in the face of complex challenges, we need a “third way” forward — blending the best of traditional agriculture with cutting-edge new technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How? COVID-19 has simultaneously paralyzed already vulnerable global food systems and ushered in food shortages — despite a surplus of technological advances. How will we continue to feed a growing population? Amanda Little has an idea: “Our challenge is to borrow from the wisdom of the ages and from our most advanced science to [a] third way: one that allows us to improve and scale our harvest while restoring, rather than degrading the underlying land of life.” Amid increasingly complex disruptions like climate change, this “third way” provides a roadmap to food security that marries old agricultural production with new, innovative farming practices — like using robots to deploy fertilizer on crop fields with sniper-like precision, eating lab-grown meats and building aeroponic farms. By nixing antiquated supply chains and producing food in a scalable, sustainable and adaptable way, Little shows just how bright our food future might be. Watch the full talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mainak Mazumdar, data scientist&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big idea: When the pursuit of using AI to make fair and equitable decisions fails, blame the data — not the algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why? The future economy won’t be built by factories and people, but by computers and algorithms — for better or for worse. To make AI possible for humanity and society, we need an urgent reset in three major areas: data infrastructure, data quality and data literacy. Together, they hold the key to ethical decision-making in the age of AI. Mazumdar lists how less-than-quality data in examples such as the 2020 US Census and marketing research could lead to poor results in trying to reach and help specific demographics. Right now, AI is only reinforcing and accelerating our bias at speed and scale, with societal implications in its wake. But it doesn’t need to be that way. Instead of racing to build new algorithms, our mission should be to build a better data infrastructure that makes ethical AI possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paul D. Miller aka DJ Spooky, multimedia musician&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Big idea: Modern computing is founded on patterns, so could you translate the patterns of code and data into music? If so, what would the internet sound like?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How? Cultural achievements throughout human history, like music and architecture, are based on pattern recognition, math and the need to organize information — and the internet is no different. Paul D. Miller aka DJ Spooky gives a tour of how the internet came to be, from the conception of software by Ada Lovelace in the early 1800s to the development of early computers catalyzed by World War II and the birth of the internet beginning in 1969. Today, millions of devices are plugged into the internet, sending data zooming around the world. By transforming the internet’s router connections and data sets into sounds, beats and tempos, Miller introduces “Quantopia,” a portrait of the internet in sound. A special auditory and visual experience, this internet soundscape reveals the patterns that connect us all.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Brian Greene, Erin Gregory, Maria Ladias and Reid Catlett</name></author><summary type="html">In a time that feels unsettled and uncertain, technology and those who create it will play a crucial role in what’s coming next. How do we define that future, as opposed to letting it define us? At a special TED Salon held as part of the Dell Technologies World conference and hosted by TED’s Simone Ross, four speakers shared ideas for building a future where tech and humanity are combined in a more active, deliberate and thoughtful way.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Join us for TEDWomen 2020: Fearless on November 12</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/23/post5.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Join us for TEDWomen 2020: Fearless on November 12" /><published>2020-10-23T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-23T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/23/post5</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/23/post5.html">&lt;p&gt;TEDWomen 2020 is nearly here! The day-long conference will take place on November 12 via TED’s new virtual conference platform. TEDWomen attendees will experience TED’s signature talks as well as an array of live, interactive sessions, community “idea dates,” small-group speaker Q&amp;amp;As and more. The talks featured in the program have been developed in collaboration with an incredible group of TEDx organizers from Lagos, Nigeria; Port of Spain, Trinidad and Tobago; Montreal, Canada; Colombo, Sri Lanka; and Sydney, Australia. TEDWomen will celebrate and amplify dynamic, multi-dimensional ideas from these communities and around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the midst of uncertainty, the greatest peril is to retreat or become immobilized. At TEDWomen, we’ll hear from bold leaders who are stepping forward and taking action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TEDWomen 2020 speakers and performers include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kluane Adamek, Assembly of First Nations Yukon Regional Chief
Kylar W. Broadus, Human and civil rights attorney and advocate
Kemi DaSilva-Ibru, Women’s health specialist
Adie Delaney, Educator and performer
Elizabeth Diller, Architect, artist and designer
Julia Gillard, 27th Prime Minister of Australia
Jamila Gordon, AI advocate
Kesha, Musician, actress, activist
María Teresa Kumar, Civic leader
JayaShri Maathaa, Monk
Megan McArthur, NASA astronaut
Madison McFerrin, Singer and songwriter
Renee Montgomery, WNBA champion and activist
Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala, Economist and international development expert
Angélique Parisot-Potter, Legal and business integrity leader
Sophie Rose, Infectious disease researcher
Apiorkor Seyiram Ashong-Abbey, Poet and author
Gloria Steinem, Feminist activist and writer
Sviatlana Tsikhanouskaya, Politician
Tracy Young, Builder
View the full speaker lineup
TED has partnered with a number of organizations to support its mission and contribute to the idea exchange at TEDWomen 2020. These organizations are collaborating with the TED team on innovative ways to engage a virtual audience and align their ideas and perspectives with this year’s programming. This year’s partners include: Boston Consulting Group, Dove Advanced Care Antiperspirant, Project Management Institute and the U.S. Air Force.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TEDWomen 2020 is taking place on November 12, 11am – 6pm ET. TEDWomen applications will be accepted until 9am ET, November 9 (or until sold out).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>TED Staff</name></author><summary type="html">TEDWomen 2020 is nearly here! The day-long conference will take place on November 12 via TED’s new virtual conference platform. TEDWomen attendees will experience TED’s signature talks as well as an array of live, interactive sessions, community “idea dates,” small-group speaker Q&amp;amp;As and more. The talks featured in the program have been developed in collaboration with an incredible group of TEDx organizers from Lagos, Nigeria; Port of Spain, Trinidad and Tobago; Montreal, Canada; Colombo, Sri Lanka; and Sydney, Australia. TEDWomen will celebrate and amplify dynamic, multi-dimensional ideas from these communities and around the world.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The making of His Holiness Pope Francis’s second TED Talk</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/10/post4.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The making of His Holiness Pope Francis’s second TED Talk" /><published>2020-10-10T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-10T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/10/post4</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/10/post4.html">&lt;p&gt;The speaker sits in front of a bookshelf, notes in hand, a deliberate tone to his voice. As we live through a pandemic and see an even bigger socio-environmental crisis quickly approaching, he says, we all face a choice: “The choice between what matters, and what doesn’t.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s how His Holiness Pope Francis frames his second TED Talk, which was livestreamed on October 10, 2020 during the closing session of the Global Launch of TED’s climate initiative, Countdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The head of the Roman Catholic Church is not new to the TED stage: he gave his first TED Talk in 2017, surprising the audience at TED’s annual conference in Vancouver via video. His acceptance to give a second TED Talk highlights his strong advocacy for action on climate change. We asked Bruno Giussani, TED’s Global Curator, who led the team that developed the Countdown program, to share the genesis of the talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What about the present moment made it the right time for Pope Francis to give a second TED Talk?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bruno Giussani: In 2015, Pope Francis published an important Encyclical letter (a book) about the environment or, in his words, about “caring for our common home.” It is called “Laudato Si’” (“Praise be to You”), and it received global attention. In it he put forward the concept of “integral ecology,” and wrote: “Although the post-industrial period may well be remembered as one of the most irresponsible in history, nonetheless there is reason to hope that humanity at the dawn of the 21st century will be remembered for having generously shouldered its grave responsibilities.” That same year, 195 countries signed the historic Paris Agreement committing to do their part to keep the increase in global temperature under 1.5 degrees Celsius and well below 2 degrees, to lower the risk of dramatic impacts of climate change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Five years later, fires, floods, droughts and hurricanes occupy the front pages. Science has never been so rich in data and so conclusive about what’s going on: we humans and our activities are changing the climate. Yet, as the data and the analysis that we have shared during Countdown show, the world is not on track to reach the targets of the Paris Agreement, and we have not really started shouldering the responsibilities the Pope wrote about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pope Francis has repeatedly referenced the need for real action and advocated for science, and I have the feeling he harbors impatience for the lack of progress. Actually, just one week before the Countdown Global Launch, he published a new Encyclical, Fratelli Tutti (Brothers All). It is a vast analysis of the current moment, discussing the twin climate and social crises, the challenges brought about by the COVID-19 pandemic and the way forward, and a renewed call for solidarity as well as personal and collective responsibility. All of these themes intersect with the intentions and goals of Countdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are the core messages of Pope Francis’s second TED Talk?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: He asks us to listen to the science. He underscores the urgency of confronting climate change and social inequity. He conveys how we won’t come out the same from the COVID-19 crisis. And he invites us to partake in what he calls “a journey of transformation and of action.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He also voices three very concrete suggestions concerning education, access to food and water, and transitioning to clean energy sources. On the latter, he makes the case for divesting from “those companies that do not meet the parameters of integral ecology,” which I understand to mean first and foremost fossil fuel companies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To whom is this talk addressed?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: As he says himself, it’s addressed to “all people of Faith, Christian or not, and all people of goodwill.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How important is it that a major religious leader is speaking on climate change?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: We live in a world where everything has become politics or profit. Face masks become a political battleground and vaccines become a race for profit, to use current examples. The role of spiritual and religious leaders in social and environmental activism is to remind us of the essential values that reside above politics and profit: those of the common good, of dialogue, inclusion and compassion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the talk, Pope Francis speaks of the future being built “not in isolation, but rather in community and in harmony.” Over the years he has convened several gatherings of scientists, businesspeople and interfaith dialogues, and he has launched many other initiatives focused on the climate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nor is this a Catholic exclusive. From the Dalai Lama to Indigenous spiritual leaders, from the Church of England to the Bahá’í, there is a lot of religious engagement for the protection of the planet and of those who live on it. In the US, there is a group of Young Evangelicals for Climate Action, for instance, and in India a few years ago, a Hindu Declaration on Climate Change was issued. But it is true that the voice of Pope Francis is of particular power and resonates well beyond the confines of the Catholic Church.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does one go about inviting the Pope to give a TED Talk?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: One goes through contacts established throughout the years and benefits from the generosity of people who opened doors and made introductions. Pope Francis gave his first TED Talk in 2017, so many at the Vatican are now familiar with TED. The demands on the Pope’s time are plenty, and we are enormously appreciative of his kindness in considering our invitation and in engaging with Countdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How was the talk prepared? TED curators usually work closely with the speakers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: We worked with several of Pope Francis’s collaborators over a period of months, discussing ideas, options and framing. In the end, of course, Pope Francis decided what he wanted to say in the talk. He was filmed by a crew from the Vatican Television Center, and then the talk was subtitled in several languages by a group of TED Translators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Pope spoke from a private study on the ground floor of the guesthouse where he lives in Vatican City. It is a rather unpretentious building called Domus Sanctae Marthae. When he became Pope, he decided to live there instead of occupying the papal apartments above St. Peter’s Square. I believe this choice manifests a genuine preference for a simpler life. But it also sends a message: that just because things have been done a certain way in the past doesn’t necessarily mean they can’t be changed. Which, of course, is a message that maps perfectly onto the climate crisis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can you tell us a little about your observations of Francis, the man? Does he have a sense of humor?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: He certainly does. He’s warm and evidently cares for people, who they are and what they think. He’s an acute observer and quick-witted. I had the privilege to be invited, together with a couple dozen other people, to the early-morning Mass that he celebrates in the private chapel at Domus Sanctae Marthae. When I met him afterwards, he pointed out immediately that he had noticed my nodding at certain passages in his sermon. I had nodded indeed: his words related to the themes of his first TED Talk. He’s also 83 years old and carries the double weight of being the spiritual leader of 1.3 billion Catholics and at the same time the head of the Church’s complex hierarchy.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>TED Staff</name></author><summary type="html">The speaker sits in front of a bookshelf, notes in hand, a deliberate tone to his voice. As we live through a pandemic and see an even bigger socio-environmental crisis quickly approaching, he says, we all face a choice: “The choice between what matters, and what doesn’t.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The making of Prince William’s TED Talk</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/10/post3.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The making of Prince William’s TED Talk" /><published>2020-10-10T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-10T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/10/post3</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/10/post3.html">&lt;p&gt;In a park close to Windsor Castle, to the West of London, is an old oak with a large protruding root. It’s sitting on that root that Prince William, The Duke of Cambridge, gives his first TED Talk as part of Countdown, TED’s climate initiative launched on October 10, 2020.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prince William’s climate engagement is known. Just two days before the Countdown Global Launch, he escalated his commitment by announcing the Earthshot Prize, a new global award for the environment to incentivize change and help repair our planet over the next ten years — a critical period for changing climate change. “The science is irrefutable. If we do not act in this decade, the damage that we have done will be irreversible and the effects felt not just by future generations, but by all of us alive today,” Prince William says in his thoughtful talk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A talk of this nature requires careful preparation. We asked Bruno Giussani, TED’s global curator and the person responsible for the Countdown program, how it came to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are the core messages of The Duke’s TED Talk?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bruno Giussani: It is an optimistic talk. Very clear on the nature and the scope of the climate challenge, but also optimistic that we can rise to the biggest challenges of our time. He takes inspiration from President John F. Kennedy’s Moonshot in the 1960s, which catalyzed, around the goal of putting a man on the Moon within a decade, the development of solutions and technologies that have then percolated into daily lives. Think, for instance, of breathing equipment, CAT scanners and solar panels. Prince William urges us to harness that same spirit of human ingenuity and purpose, and turn it, to use his words, towards “the most pressing challenge we have ever faced: repairing the planet.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From Moonshot to Earthshot. Tell us about the Earthshot Prize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: It is a compelling and ambitious vision. The Prize is centered around five clear goals — or Earthshots — underpinned by science-based targets to trigger and accelerate new ways of thinking as well as new technologies, policies and solutions for the planet. The five goals are: protect and restore nature; clean our air; revive the oceans; build a waste-free world; and fix our climate. Starting next year and until 2030, the Prize will be awarded every year to five winners, one per Earthshot. The awards are each worth £1 million GBP (about $1.3 million USD).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the Earthshot Prize is a strategic partner of Countdown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: Yes, the two initiatives are quite complementary, both global in nature, built on a collaborative approach and rooted in science. We look forward to continuing the collaboration with Prince William and The Royal Foundation of The Duke and Duchess of Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How does one go about inviting Prince William to give a TED Talk?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: We had been thinking about inviting Prince William for a while, we were just waiting for the right opportunity. When a member of the TED community alerted us about the work The Duke’s team is doing on the Earthshot Prize and how it mapped onto the aims of Countdown, we felt that the moment had come. We engaged preliminary discussions with his brilliant team, which rapidly led to his decision to accept the invitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why do you think he agreed to doing this talk?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: He is very focused right now on the climate and ecological emergency. The Earthshot Prize has a real chance to contribute to accelerating solutions, and it could change the narrative to one of excitement and opportunity. In the talk, Prince William was able to set out his vision of how we can bring a sense of optimism and hope to meet the challenge of this moment. In his own words: “I’m determined to both start and end this decade as an optimist”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did Prince William write his own talk?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: Like every person in his position, The Duke has collaborators helping prepare his public speeches. This was no different. We discussed ideas, drafts and framing, and we had a very productive discussion with him — via videoconference of course. At the end, obviously, he decided what he wanted to keep in the talk and what not. If you watch it, you will immediately appreciate the genuine and deeply felt nature of the message he’s conveying from under that old oak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is The Duke of Cambridge like?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: Prince William is remarkably humble and approachable for someone who has spent his whole life in the public eye. His constant focus on how to get things done gives the strong impression of someone who is very determined to make an impact on the world and will use all resources he has available to him to do it. He asks good questions and listens carefully to the answers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who filmed the talk?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BG: You are right to point that out: the talk is filmed in an intensely simple — a man under a tree — yet very powerful way. It was filmed by great British documentary producer, Alastair Fothergill. Among other titles to his credit, he was the series producer of world-famous nature documentaries such as The Blue Planet and Planet Earth.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>TED Staff</name></author><summary type="html">In a park close to Windsor Castle, to the West of London, is an old oak with a large protruding root. It’s sitting on that root that Prince William, The Duke of Cambridge, gives his first TED Talk as part of Countdown, TED’s climate initiative launched on October 10, 2020.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Are you ready for the Countdown Global Launch? Tune in Saturday, 10.10.2020</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/06/post1.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Are you ready for the Countdown Global Launch? Tune in Saturday, 10.10.2020" /><published>2020-10-06T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-06T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/06/post1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/06/post1.html">&lt;p&gt;Grab your friends and family, and tune in to YouTube.com/TED for the Countdown Global Launch this Saturday, October 10, 2020 at 11am ET.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TED’s first-ever free conference, the Global Launch kicks off Countdown, a global initiative to champion and accelerate solutions to the climate crisis. This weekend’s virtual event will explain why the climate crisis is so urgent, share ideas from experts in a range of fields and call on leaders and citizens everywhere to take action. Expect a day packed with more than 50 speakers, activists, actors and musicians in five curated sessions of actionable and science-backed ideas paired with moments of wonder, inspiration and optimism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This special event will feature hosts Jane Fonda, Priyanka Chopra Jonas, Chris Hemsworth, Mark Ruffalo, Don Cheadle, Al Gore, Xiye Bastida, Prajakta Koli, Hannah Stocking and Jaden Smith; and speakers Prince William, His Holiness Pope Francis, Monica Araya, Jesper Brodin, Dave Clark, Christiana Figueres, Kara Hurst, Lisa Jackson, Rose M. Mutiso, Johan Rockström, Nigel Topping, Ursula von der Leyen and many more; with special musical performances by Prince Royce, Sigrid and Yemi Alade.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Countdown Global Launch, presented by TED and Future Stewards, will run from 11am – 5pm ET. Segments from the event, including the biggest talks and performances, will be made available immediately across TED’s digital platforms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information and to #JoinTheCountdown, visit countdown.ted.com and follow along live this Saturday on Twitter, Instagram and Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>TED Staff</name></author><summary type="html">Grab your friends and family, and tune in to YouTube.com/TED for the Countdown Global Launch this Saturday, October 10, 2020 at 11am ET.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">TED announces an exciting new slate of podcasts</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/09/30/post2.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="TED announces an exciting new slate of podcasts" /><published>2020-09-30T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-09-30T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/09/30/post2</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/09/30/post2.html">&lt;p&gt;Pindrop returns&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Escape with host Saleem Reshamwala and journey across the globe in search of the world’s most surprising and imaginative ideas. Pindrop isn’t a travel show, exactly. It’s a deep dive into the ideas that shape a particular spot on the map, brought to you by the people who live there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New episodes will take listeners to Lima, Peru, where hip-hop artists are trying to save an endangered language (and restore the nation’s pride along the way); then over to Rapa Nui (aka Easter Island), one of the most remote places on earth, where the pandemic has inspired a complete reimagining of island life; and on a road trip to find a real-life Black utopia in North Carolina — and the possibilities it inspires for future generations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pindrop is made possible with support from Marriott Hotels and Women Will, a Grow with Google program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pindrop returns with four new episodes beginning October 14.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Design Matters joins the family&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A show about how incredibly creative people design the arc of their lives, the iconic Design Matters with Debbie Millman will join the TED family in October. It’s the world’s first podcast about design: an inquiry into the broader world of creative culture through wide-ranging conversations with designers, writers, artists, curators, musicians and other luminaries of contemporary thought. Design Matters will continue to be produced independently, with TED amplifying the podcast to its global audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Design Matters episodes are available on TED platforms in October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely, X is free and available to the public&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some ideas are too risky to share in the open. Sincerely, X is a space to share those controversial ideas anonymously. Hosted by poet, performer and educator Sarah Kay, this powerful show is a window into stories that usually stay hidden, an honest look at experiences typically too painful or difficult to share.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Previously only on the Luminary app, season two is being made available on all podcast platforms. In the first episode, we hear from a small-town preacher in the Deep South with a radical secret: he doesn’t believe in hell. We’ll also meet a sociopath who reveals what society can learn from her condition; a former cult member who teaches us how to let go of the past; and much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely, X episodes drop on TED’s platforms October 22, with a new episode every week for 10 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also from TED…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TED Business, hosted by Modupe Akinola, associate professor of management at Columbia Business School, will take listeners through some of the most creative and surprising TED Talks that illuminate the business world. Strictly business topics are just the beginning: TED Business will also dig into relevant talks on psychology, science, design, democracy — stretching listeners’ sense of what really matters in business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Episodes available weekly, starting October 12&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TED Health provides a curated selection of the best health-related TED Talks. From smart daily habits to new medical breakthroughs, doctors and researchers share discoveries and ideas about medicine and well-being.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Episodes available weekly, starting October 13&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Twenty Thousand Hertz is hosted by Dallas Taylor, creative director of Defacto Sound. The lovingly crafted podcast reveals the stories behind the world’s most recognizable and interesting sounds. In upcoming episodes, modern paleontology shares what dinosaurs really sound like (October 7) and how we might create a sonic utopia in the future (November 11).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New episodes available every other Wednesday&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TED Talks Daily, TED’s flagship podcast, will begin publishing talks from Countdown — a global initiative to combat climate change — beginning in mid-October. The first TED Talk to publish will be from Prince William, The Duke of Cambridge, followed by talks from climate impact scholar Johan Rockström, electrification advocate Monica Araya and UK parliament member David Lammy. These talks will also be published in a special Countdown podcast to showcase the most exciting ideas about fighting climate change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Talks from Countdown will begin publishing October 10&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TED Radio Hour investigates the biggest questions of our time with the help of the world’s greatest thinkers. Can we preserve our humanity in the digital age? Where does creativity come from? And what’s the secret to living longer? In each episode, host Manoush Zomorodi explores a big idea through a series of TED Talks and original interviews, inspiring us to learn more about the world, our communities and, most importantly, ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In October, TED Radio Hour will release an exciting episode featuring the cohost of NPR’s All Things Considered Mary Louise Kelly, biophysicist and neuroscientist Jim Hudspeth, writer and “part-time cyborg” Rebecca Knill, musician and acoustic engineer Renzo Vitale and TED’s own Dallas Taylor, the host of Twenty Thousand Hertz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New episodes available every Friday&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our partners: TED strives to tell partner stories in the form of authentic, story-driven content developed in real time and aligned with the editorial process — finding and exploring brilliant ideas from all over the world. This season’s podcasts are made possible with support from Change Healthcare, Lexus, Marriott Hotels, Women Will, a Grow with Google program, and more.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>TED Staff</name></author><summary type="html">Pindrop returns</summary></entry></feed>